[
  {
    "problem": "6 + 2 =",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "problem": "9 + 6 =",
    "answer": 15
  },
  {
    "problem": "6 + 5 =",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "problem": "5 + 5 =",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "problem": "7 + 3 =",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "problem": "1 + 6 =",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "problem": "5 + 4 =",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "problem": "8 + 9 =",
    "answer": 17
  },
  {
    "problem": "6 + 3 =",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "problem": "1 + 6 =",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "problem": "8 + 1 =",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "problem": "7 + 4 =",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "problem": "8 + 6 =",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "problem": "8 + 8 =",
    "answer": 16
  },
  {
    "problem": "4 + 3 =",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "problem": "6 + 9 =",
    "answer": 15
  },
  {
    "problem": "8 + 7 =",
    "answer": 15
  },
  {
    "problem": "8 + 9 =",
    "answer": 17
  },
  {
    "problem": "8 + 4 =",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "problem": "5 + 9 =",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "problem": "2 + 9 =",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "problem": "7 + 5 =",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "problem": "7 + 6 =",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "problem": "2 + 9 =",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "problem": "3 + 2 =",
    "answer": 5
  },
  {
    "problem": "6 + 1 =",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "problem": "1 + 4 =",
    "answer": 5
  },
  {
    "problem": "9 + 9 =",
    "answer": 18
  },
  {
    "problem": "7 + 3 =",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "problem": "4 + 7 =",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "problem": "1 + 8 =",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "problem": "7 + 1 =",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "problem": "3 + 5 =",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "problem": "8 + 5 =",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "problem": "4 + 7 =",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "problem": "2 + 9 =",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "problem": "5 + 7 =",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "problem": "5 + 7 =",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "problem": "5 + 9 =",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "problem": "9 + 1 =",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "problem": "2 + 7 =",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "problem": "1 + 9 =",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "problem": "4 + 7 =",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "problem": "1 + 3 =",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "problem": "4 + 8 =",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "problem": "1 + 7 =",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "problem": "6 + 6 =",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "problem": "6 + 4 =",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "problem": "5 + 9 =",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "problem": "6 + 4 =",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "problem": "3 + 8 =",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "problem": "9 + 6 =",
    "answer": 15
  },
  {
    "problem": "3 + 8 =",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "problem": "9 + 5 =",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "problem": "4 + 9 =",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "problem": "9 + 4 =",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "problem": "8 + 8 =",
    "answer": 16
  },
  {
    "problem": "5 + 7 =",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "problem": "4 + 8 =",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "problem": "6 + 3 =",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "problem": "5 + 2 =",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "problem": "4 + 8 =",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "problem": "7 + 5 =",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "problem": "8 + 9 =",
    "answer": 17
  },
  {
    "problem": "8 + 5 =",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "problem": "7 + 5 =",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "problem": "5 + 6 =",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "problem": "1 + 7 =",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "problem": "7 + 6 =",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "problem": "2 + 3 =",
    "answer": 5
  },
  {
    "problem": "7 + 2 =",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "problem": "1 + 6 =",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "problem": "9 + 7 =",
    "answer": 16
  },
  {
    "problem": "3 + 4 =",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "problem": "7 + 1 =",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "problem": "2 + 9 =",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "problem": "4 + 7 =",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "problem": "3 + 6 =",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "problem": "6 + 9 =",
    "answer": 15
  },
  {
    "problem": "1 + 8 =",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "problem": "8 + 2 =",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "problem": "4 + 8 =",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "problem": "1 + 4 =",
    "answer": 5
  },
  {
    "problem": "8 + 2 =",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "problem": "6 + 9 =",
    "answer": 15
  },
  {
    "problem": "6 + 4 =",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "problem": "5 + 6 =",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "problem": "7 + 4 =",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "problem": "7 + 8 =",
    "answer": 15
  },
  {
    "problem": "5 + 9 =",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "problem": "2 + 3 =",
    "answer": 5
  },
  {
    "problem": "9 + 7 =",
    "answer": 16
  },
  {
    "problem": "8 + 5 =",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "problem": "7 + 7 =",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "problem": "6 + 9 =",
    "answer": 15
  },
  {
    "problem": "8 + 4 =",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "problem": "7 + 9 =",
    "answer": 16
  },
  {
    "problem": "8 + 3 =",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "problem": "4 + 2 =",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "problem": "9 + 6 =",
    "answer": 15
  }
]